http://www.lazinc.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Who are we?
We are Lazinc Limited trading as Lazinc. Our company number is 05091966 and our registered office address is 2 Jardine House, The Harrovian Business Village, Bessborough Road, Harrow, Middlesex HA1 3EX. Our VAT number is 839 8869 44.
Lazinc takes data protection seriously
We keep to a minimum the information we hold about you
We use your data to provide our services to you, respond to your enquiries, manage our relationship with you, meet our legal obligations, and to improve our website
We delete your data when it is no longer needed for these things
Generally, we do not give your information to third parties, but there are some exceptions
You have privacy rights as an individual
We don’t record calls
We are happy to talk to you about how we process and protect your data
If Lazinc Limited, at some point in the future, chooses to sell, merge, divest or transfer any part of our business then your data will be transferred to the new business and used in accordance with this privacy policy. The lawful basis for processing in this scenario is legitimate interest, since evolving our company is a legitimate thing for us to do.
Tell me more…
To see more about how we use your personal data, read the notice or notices which apply best to your relationship with us:
I am just looking at your website
What data we hold
We generate log files from various servers: this will include an IP address assigned to you or, more likely, to someone who provides you with Internet access
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website in order to provide increased functionality and service. This not only helps us to provide you with a better experience, but also to help us improve our website and services
Unless you have adjusted your web browser settings (if and where possible) to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our website or related online services. However, in doing so, you may find that certain functionality or services may be impaired or unavailable to you
The cookies we use only contain anonymous information to improve the services we offer, and do not contain personal information
It is also important to point out that not all cookies used by this website are created by us. These cookies (referred to as third party cookies) are covered below:
Google Analytics
Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  Google can provide more details about their cookies.
Facebook Users
Facebook uses cookies to track visitors to our business page. These cookies are set even if you do not have a Facebook account. They will track your Internet activities on and off Facebook. Despite the fact that only Facebook has access to the data from these cookies, not us, by creating and maintaining a Facebook business page, we are deemed responsible for the cookies being set. We have no way to prevent these cookies being used. We want to be as transparent as possible so you are aware of the way your data is being used by Facebook.
Using Your Information
Technical data
We may use the logs from our servers to assist in our firm's security, as well as to determine visitor behaviour and help us plan our strategy (e.g. such as working out which pages on the site are most popular, or whether particular events have caused an increase in traffic).
The legal basis for processing this data is that we have legal and regulatory obligations to protect our clients and their information, also strategy planning is a legitimate thing for a business to do.
Transfers of your data
We do not transfer or process data outside the EEA or other countries deemed to have inadequate protection of data by the EU.
Third parties
As a general principle, we will not transfer your personal data to third parties without your permission. That will usually be a third party who is interested in purchasing your art or working with you in the future.
We also have a small number of companies providing services to us. These are our processors and we have confirmed that they all meet the requirements of the GDPR.
Your rights
You have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on privacy@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
I am an artist displaying my work with you
What data we hold
As an artist that we have a business relationship with, we will hold the following personal information about you:
Your name, contact details, bank details and, if you have provided it, your ID
Details of the technical personal data that we process is below:
We generate log files from various servers when you visit our website: this will include an IP address assigned to you or, more likely, to someone who provides you with Internet access Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website in order to provide increased functionality and service. This not only helps us to provide you with a better experience, but also to help us improve our website and services
Unless you have adjusted your web browser settings (if and where possible) to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our website or related online services. However, in doing so, you may find that certain functionality or services may be impaired or unavailable to you
The cookies we use only contain anonymous information to improve the services we offer, and do not contain personal information
Our website, like many others, uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  Google can provide more details about their cookies
Using Your Information
Lazinc is a contemporary art gallery which has been championing innovative artists since 2006. Lazinc is a international market leader in street art and supports a variety of artists including JR, Invader, Todd James, Antony Micallef and Jonathan Yeo.
We use the information we hold about you in order to best showcase your art and to connect you with people that we believe to be interested in your artworks.
The legal basis for processing this data is that we have a legitimate interest in processing this data to identify which work is yours, and to contact you if a third party expresses an interest in working with you.
We hold your contact details and bank details so that we can pay you.
The legal basis for processing this data is that this is necessary for us to meet our contractual obligations with you.
In some cases you have provided your ID data, which we use to book travel for you; this is a legitimate thing for us to do.
Technical data
We may use the logs from our servers to assist in our firm's security, as well as to determine visitor behaviour and help us plan our strategy (e.g. such as working out which pages on the site are most popular, or whether particular events have caused an increase in traffic).
The legal basis for processing this data is that we have legal and regulatory obligations to protect our clients and their information, also strategy planning is a legitimate thing for a business to do.
Transfers of your data
Almost all of our data is held in the European Economic Area (EEA), but we do transfer or process data some outside the EEA because we use third party cloud storage providers whose servers are based in the US. These parties are signed up to the US Privacy Shield (https://www.privacyshield.gov/list ) which means the EU considers them to have adequate measures in place, in line with EU data protection laws, to protect your personal data.
Retention periods
We keep your contact details for as long as we consider you to be a current or potential artist that we have/may have a business relationship with. We delete your ID details after use and your bank details at the end of our contractual obligation with you, or as long as we are legally obliged to do so.
Third parties
As a general principle, we will not transfer your personal data to third parties without your permission. That will usually be a third party who is interested in purchasing your art or working with you in the future.
We also have a small number of companies providing services to us. These are our processors and we have confirmed that they all meet the requirements of the GDPR.
Technical security
All our laptops are password protected, as are our phones
Our phones are fully encrypted
Our servers and desktop computers are protected by physical security
The ability to log on to all these devices is restricted to members of staff, each having their own unique log on credentials
Landline phone calls are not encrypted
If you have particular security requirements, please call us to discuss how we can support you
Call recording
We do not record telephone calls. This may change in the future: if it does, we will let you know.
Facebook Users
Facebook uses cookies to track visitors to our business page. These cookies are set even if you do not have a Facebook account. They will track your Internet activities on and off Facebook. Despite the fact that only Facebook has access to the data from these cookies, not us, by creating and maintaining a Facebook business page, we are deemed responsible for the cookies being set. We have no way to prevent these cookies being used. We want to be as transparent as possible so you are aware of the way your data is being used by Facebook.
Your rights
You have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on privacy@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
I am a supplier
If you are a supplier then this information applies to you:
Lazinc takes data protection seriously.
We keep to a minimum the information we hold about you
We use your data to consider using your goods/service, respond to your enquiries, manage our relationship with you, meet our legal obligations, including paying you, and improve our website
We delete your data when it is no longer needed for these things
Generally, we do not give your information to third parties, but there are some exceptions
You have privacy rights as an individual
We don’t record calls
We are happy to talk to you about how we process and protect your data
What data we hold
We may hold the following information about you:
Your name and contact information
Your payment details
Technical personal data if you use our website (details of this below)
We generate log files from various servers when you visit our website: this will include an IP address assigned to you or, more likely, to someone who provides you with Internet access. Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website in order to provide increased functionality and service. This not only helps us to provide you with a better experience, but also to help us improve our website and services
Unless you have adjusted your web browser settings (if and where possible) to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our website or related online services. However, in doing so, you may find that certain functionality or services may be impaired or unavailable to you
The cookies we use only contain anonymous information to improve the services we offer, and do not contain personal information
Our website, like many others, uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  Google can provide more details about their cookies
Using your information
Dealing with your enquiry
If you call us or make contact by email, we will follow up on your enquiry and see if there is a way in which we can help you. We keep a record of enquiries received, so that we know what we have said to whom.
The legal basis for processing this data is that we need to use your details to follow up with you. It is also legitimate for us to keep track of what we have said to you so we can understand further business need and plan our strategy accordingly.
We will use your data to manage our relationship with you, to enquire about/buy products and services from you, and to pay you.
We need to use your details to enter into and perform contracts with you, as well as keeping track of what we have agreed.
Recommending you
We have some great suppliers, and we love to recommend them to others where we think it might be helpful. Recommending you is a legitimate thing for a business to do.
Technical data
We may use the logs from our servers to assist in our firm's security, as well as to determine visitor behaviour and help us plan our strategy (e.g. such as working out which pages on the site are most popular, or whether particular events have caused an increase in traffic).
We have legal and regulatory obligations to protect our suppliers and their information, and strategy planning is a legitimate thing for a business to do.
Transfers of your data
We do not transfer or process data outside the EEA or other countries deemed to have inadequate protection of data by the EU.
Retention periods
We will retain your contact details as long as we have a relationship with you or think we might want to buy products or services from you, or for the duration of a dispute with you.
Third parties
As a general principle, we will not transfer your personal data to third parties without your permission.
We also have a small number of companies providing services to us. These are our processors and we have confirmed that they all meet the requirements of the GDPR.
Technical security
All our laptops are full-disk encrypted, as are our phones and tablets.
Our servers and desktop computers are protected by physical security.
The ability to log on to all these devices is restricted to members of staff, each having their own unique log on credentials.
Landline phone calls are not encrypted.
If you have particular security requirements, please email us on privacy@lazinc.com to discuss how we can support you.
Call recording
We do not record telephone calls. This may change in the future: if it does, we will let you know.
Facebook Users
Facebook uses cookies to track visitors to our business page. These cookies are set even if you do not have a Facebook account. They will track your Internet activities on and off Facebook. Despite the fact that only Facebook has access to the data from these cookies, not us, by creating and maintaining a Facebook business page, we are deemed responsible for the cookies being set. We have no way to prevent these cookies being used. We want to be as transparent as possible so you are aware of the way your data is being used by Facebook.
Your rights
As a supplier, you have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on privacy@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
I am an employee
If you are an employee, please refer to our employee handbook and MyHRToolkit for information about how we use your personal data, or email the Data Protection Lead: privacy@lazinc.com
I am a potential employee
Summary
Lazinc takes data protection seriously
We keep to a minimum the information we hold about you
We use your data to provide our services to you, respond to your enquiries, manage our relationship with you, meet our legal obligations, and to improve our website
We delete your data when it is no longer needed for these things
Generally, we do not give your information to third parties, but there are some exceptions
You have privacy rights as an individual
We don’t record calls
We are happy to talk to you about how we process and protect your data
What we hold
If you have applied for a job with us then we will hold the following information until such time as your application for a specific role is either successful or unsuccessful:
The information that you provided on your CV or application form.
If you attend an interview, we will hold interview notes.
If your application is successful then your data is processed as per the Fair Processing Notice available in the employee handbook and MyHRtoolkit
If your application is unsuccessful then your CV and interview notes will be stored for 3 months just in case there are any disputes on either side, or if that particular role becomes vacant again
If you call us or make contact by email, we will follow up on your enquiry and see if there is a way in which we can help you. We keep a record of enquiries received, so that we know what we have said to whom
Technical personal data is also captured if you use our website and that is processed to protect our users from cyber attacks and also for us to see which areas of our website are being used the most, which in term helps us with our strategy planning: a legitimate thing for companies to do
Note: we do not accept unsolicited CVs; these are deleted immediately. We also do not keep CVs beyond what we have stated above. CVs go out of data quickly and we have an obligation to have correct data in our systems, as well as having a lawful reason for holding it. “Just in case” is not a good reason.
Details of the technical personal data that we process is below
We generate log files from various servers when you visit our website: this will include an IP address assigned to you or, more likely, to someone who provides you with Internet access
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website in order to provide increased functionality and service. This not only helps us to provide you with a better experience, but also to help us improve our website and services.
Unless you have adjusted your web browser settings (if and where possible) to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our website or related online services. However, in doing so, you may find that certain functionality or services may be impaired or unavailable to you
The cookies we use only contain anonymous information to improve the services we offer, and do not contain personal information
Our website, like many others, uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  Google can provide more details about their cookies
Using Your Information
The data we hold on you will be with the intention of starting a contract with you, or because of a legitimate business interest, such as holding interview notes.
Technical data
We may use the logs from our servers to assist in our firm's security, as well as to determine visitor behaviour and help us plan our strategy (e.g. such as working out which pages on the site are most popular, or whether particular events have caused an increase in traffic).
The legal basis for processing this data is that we have legal and regulatory obligations to protect our clients and their information, also strategy planning is a legitimate thing for a business to do.
Transfers of your data
We do not transfer or process data outside the EEA or other countries deemed to have inadequate protection of data by the EU.
Third parties
We also have a small number of companies providing services to us. These are our processors and we have confirmed that they all meet the requirements of EU data protection laws.
Technical security
All our laptops are password protected, as are our phones
Our phones are fully encrypted
Our servers and desktop computers are protected by physical security
The ability to log on to all these devices is restricted to members of staff, each having their own unique log on credentials
Landline phone calls are not encrypted
If you have particular security requirements, please email us on privacy@lazinc.com to discuss how we can support you.
Call recording
We do not record telephone calls. This may change in the future: if it does, we will let you know.
Your rights
You have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on privacy@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
I am someone who may want to buy art and/or has signed up to your newsletter
What data we hold
We will hold your contact details if we believe you are someone who may be interested in purchasing works by our artists or potentially working with them in some capacity, or if you have requested to receive updates about our gallery or print studio. These details will have been gained by you initiating contact with us, through a previous interaction with one of our team in a similar capacity, or through an online platform.
We will use this data to keep you updated if you have requested so, and we may also use this data to send you information about artworks that we believe to be of interest to you.
If you contact us, we will follow up on your enquiry and see if there is a way in which we can help you. We keep a record of enquiries received, so that we know what we have said to whom.
We hold this data based on legitimate interest; we believe it is to the benefit of both us and you that we have your details.
If you requested to stay updated with our news about the gallery and print studio then we hold this data based on consent.
We also abide by the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations (PECR) when we contact you. We will only email you if you are an existing customer. If you are not an existing customer then we will only email you if you have given your clear consent for us to do so. We will only phone you if we have confirmed that you are not on a suppression list.
Your details will be held on encrypted and password protected devices, which have a remote wipe function, should the need arise.
We hold the data on you until such point as you ask us to remove your details, or tell us that you are no longer interested in hearing from us.
As an interested party, you have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on info@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Transfers of Data
Like many EU businesses, we transfer data to Mailchimp who act as a processor for our marketing emails and/or newsletters. Mailchimp also act as a controller for some of your data once this is passed to them. We recommend therefore that you read their privacy policy here to understand exactly what they do with this data, and see how you can opt out of them using your data for analytics purposes.
We are aware that Mailchimp expects us to have got permission for your data to be used this way, but we do not believe that we are in a position to get consent on behalf of another company when we have no control over how they use the data.
Facebook Users
Facebook uses cookies to track visitors to our business page. These cookies are set even if you do not have a Facebook account. They will track your Internet activities on and off Facebook. Despite the fact that only Facebook has access to the data from these cookies, not us, by creating and maintaining a Facebook business page, we are deemed responsible for the cookies being set. We have no way to prevent these cookies being used. We want to be as transparent as possible so you are aware of the way your data is being used by Facebook.
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
I am a customer
Lazinc takes data protection seriously
We keep to a minimum the information we hold about you
We use your data to provide our services to you, respond to your enquiries, manage our relationship with you, meet our legal obligations, and to improve our website
We delete your data when it is no longer needed for these things
Generally, we do not give your information to third parties, but there are some exceptions
You have privacy rights as an individual
We don’t record calls
We are happy to talk to you about how we process and protect your data
What data we hold
As one of our customers, we will hold the following personal information about you for the length of time that we consider you to an existing customer:
The information that is needed to fulfil our contract with you. This will be your contact details (we need to know who you are) and any delivery detail you gave us. Also, because you need to pay for the items, we have your payment details purely for the length of time of the transaction. If you are an online shopper, we do not have your payment details
Because you are an existing customer, we will contact you from time to time to let you know about our goods and services that may be of interest to you
If you call us or make contact by email, we will follow up on your enquiry and see if there is a way in which we can help you. We keep a record of enquiries received, so that we know what we have said to whom
Technical personal data is also captured if you use the website
Details of the technical personal data that we process is below
We generate log files from various servers when you visit our website: this will include an IP address assigned to you or, more likely, to someone who provides you with Internet access
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website in order to provide increased functionality and service. This not only helps us to provide you with a better experience, but also to help us improve our website and services
Unless you have adjusted your web browser settings (if and where possible) to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our website or related online services. However, in doing so, you may find that certain functionality or services may be impaired or unavailable to you
The cookies we use only contain anonymous information to improve the services we offer, and do not contain personal information
Our website, like many others, uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  Google can provide more details about their cookies
We may use the logs from our servers to assist in our firm's security, as well as to determine visitor behaviour and help us plan our strategy (e.g. such as working out which pages on the site are most popular, or whether particular events have caused an increase in traffic). We have legal and regulatory obligations to protect our clients and their information and strategy planning is a legitimate thing for a business to do.
Using Your Information
We use your information to maintain our side of the sale contract with you and for delivery purposes.
We hold contact details to tell you upcoming exhibitions or artists, and about artworks. We do this because we think you would benefit from this, and we might too. We will always give you the option to opt out of receiving marketing emails from us and if you do that we won’t send you marketing emails again.
If you visit our website, technical data processed to protect our users from cyber-attacks and also for us to see which bits of our website are being used the most, which in turn helps us with our strategy planning, a legitimate thing for companies to do.
Transfers of your data
We do not transfer or process data outside the EEA or other countries deemed to have inadequate protection of data by the EU.
Third parties
We also have a small number of companies providing services to us including carriers and payment services. These are our processors and we have confirmed that they all meet the requirements of EU data protection laws.
Technical security
Landline phone calls are not encrypted.
If you have particular security requirements, please email us on privacy@lazinc.com to discuss how we can support you.
Call recording
We do not record telephone calls. This may change in the future: if it does, we will let you know.
Facebook Users
Facebook uses cookies to track visitors to our business page. These cookies are set even if you do not have a Facebook account. They will track your Internet activities on and off Facebook. Despite the fact that only Facebook has access to the data from these cookies, not us, by creating and maintaining a Facebook business page, we are deemed responsible for the cookies being set. We have no way to prevent these cookies being used. We want to be as transparent as possible so you are aware of the way your data is being used by Facebook.
Your rights
You have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on privacy@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
I am a seller
If you trust is to consign your art, then this information applies to you:
Lazinc takes data protection seriously.
We keep to a minimum the information we hold about you
We use your data to consider using your goods/service, respond to your enquiries, manage our relationship with you, meet our legal obligations, including paying you, and improve our website
We delete your data when it is no longer needed for these things
Generally, we do not give your information to third parties, but there are some exceptions
You have privacy rights as an individual
We don’t record calls
We are happy to talk to you about how we process and protect your data
What data we hold
We may hold the following information about you:
Your name and contact information
Your payment details
Details of the technical personal data that we process if you use our website is below
We generate log files from various servers when you visit our website: this will include an IP address assigned to you or, more likely, to someone who provides you with Internet access
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website in order to provide increased functionality and service. This not only helps us to provide you with a better experience, but also to help us improve our website and services
Unless you have adjusted your web browser settings (if and where possible) to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our website or related online services. However, in doing so, you may find that certain functionality or services may be impaired or unavailable to you
The cookies we use only contain anonymous information to improve the services we offer, and do not contain personal information
Our website, like many others, uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.  Google can provide more details about their cookies
Using your information
If you call us or make contact by email, we will follow up on your enquiry and see if there is a way in which we can help you. We keep a record of enquiries received, so that we know what we have said to whom.
The legal basis for processing this data is that we need to use your details to follow up with you. It is also legitimate for us to keep track of what we said to you so we can understand further business need and plan our strategy accordingly.
We need to use your details to enter into and perform contracts with you, as well as keeping track of what terms have been agreed.
Transfers of your data
We do not transfer or process data outside the EEA or other countries deemed to have inadequate protection of data by the EU.
Retention periods
For as long as we have a relationship with you or think we might want to buy products or services from you, or for the duration of a dispute with you.
Third parties
As a general principle, we will not transfer your personal data to third parties without your permission.
We also have a small number of companies providing services to us. These are our processors and we have confirmed that they all meet the requirements of the GDPR.
Technical security
All our laptops are full-disk encrypted, as are our phones and tablets
Our servers and desktop computers are protected by physical security
The ability to log on to all these devices is restricted to members of staff, each having their own unique log on credentials
Landline phone calls are not encrypted
If you have particular security requirements, please email us on privacy@lazinc.com to discuss how we can support you.
Call recording
We do not record telephone calls. This may change in the future: if it does, we will let you know.
Facebook Users
Facebook uses cookies to track visitors to our business page. These cookies are set even if you do not have a Facebook account. They will track your Internet activities on and off Facebook. Despite the fact that only Facebook has access to the data from these cookies, not us, by creating and maintaining a Facebook business page, we are deemed responsible for the cookies being set. We have no way to prevent these cookies being used. We want to be as transparent as possible so you are aware of the way your data is being used by Facebook.
Your rights
You have rights concerning your personal data. You are entitled to:
Request a copy of your personal data and information about our processing of it
Request that we delete information on you if we do not need to hold it
Request that we correct any personal data that we hold on you
Request that we stop processing your data, although we can still hold it (e.g. on a suppression list, so that we know not to call you again)
Request that we move your data to another organisation’s IT system electronically
You also have the right to withdraw your consent
If you want to exercise any of these rights, please contact us on privacy@lazinc.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with a supervisory authority. In the UK the supervisory authority is the ICO, whose details are here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/postal-addresses/
Contact us
If you want to talk to us about this, please email privacy@lazinc.com
For wheelchair access, please contact the gallery prior to your visit.
Exclusive prints and editions right at your fingertips...
Browse Originals
Buy original works by our artists, starting at £1,000
Browse Editions
Buy exclusive prints and editions by our artists, starting at £100
Sell your art
Contact us to sell originals or editions through Lazinc.
For wheelchair access, please contact the gallery prior to your visit.
Minimum price you would accept (GBP)
Sign up to our mailing list to be the first to know about exclusive print releases, exhibition announcements and general Lazinc news.
Join our mailing list
Close
Please wait
We are checking availability of your items.
If available we will process your payment.
Please do not refresh this page.
This site uses cookies to improve user experience. By clicking ‘Accept’ or by continuing to use this site, you consent to our use of cookies.
Learn more about our cookies policy
Accept
Skip video
